Guide to the Frank Moore Papers MSS.135
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI: Miller's Wife
  - Subseries A: Production Elements
    - Video Production Element: Scratchtrack Master "The Miller's Wife" Rough Cut Dub - Silent, [undated]; ID: 135.0173 (Box 23B, Media ID: 135.0173)
      Video Recording, [60:00], Eastman Kodak EK30 KCA Proffessional EP-930 Video Cassette
    - Video Production Element: Window Dub "Miller's Wife" - A. Leroy Dialogue - Sound EFX, [undated]; ID: 135.0174 (Box 23B, Media ID: 135.0174)
    - Video Production Element: "The Miller's Wife" Dub, [undated]; ID: 135.0176 (Box 23B, Media ID: 135.0176)
      Video Recording, [60:00], Sony Videogenix Cassette
    - Video Production Element: "The Miller's Wife" (Work in Progress) Transfer from 16mm Workprint, 1988-1990; ID: 135.0255 (Box 23B, Media ID: 135.0255)
      Video Recording, [60:00], Sony KCA-60XBR Video Cassette
    - Video Production Element: "Miller's Wife" Work Sample 6/4/90, ID: 135.0256 (Box 23B, Media ID: 135.0256)
      Video Recording, [03:00], Sony Video Cassette
    - Video Production Element: "Miller's Wife" Work Sample 6/4/90, ID: 135.0257 (Box 23B, Media ID: 135.0257)
      Video Recording, [03:00], TS-15-S Video Cassette
    - Audio Production Elements: 1/4" reel to reel, 1988-1990 (Box 23C, Folder ID: 135.0177-135.0178)
  - Subseries B: Technical Notations and Lab Related Paperwork
    - 135.0169A Dialogue, undated (Box 23, Folder 982)
    - 135.0175A Audio log, undated (Box 23, Folder 983)
    - 135.0177A Tape log, undated (Box 23, Folder 984)
    - 135.0178A tape log, undated (Box 23, Folder 985)
    - 135.0179A timing strip, work order, purchase order, printing and cleaning report, labels, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 986)
    - 135.0180A Timing strip, work order, order form, printing and cleaning report, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 987)
    - 135.0183A work order, timing strip, P.O., camera report, negative cleaning report, lab order, timer's listing, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 988)
    - 135.0184A Timing strip, work order, P.O., Negative printing and cleaning report, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 989)
    - 135.0185A Printing and negative cleaning report, edge number notes, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 990)
    - 135.0186A, timing strip, work order, P.O., printing and negative cleaning report, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 991)
    - 135.0187A, printing and negative cleaning report, timing strip, timer's listing and misc. papers, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 992)
    - 135.0188A, timing strip, work order, p.o., printing and negative cleaning report, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 993)
    - 135.0190A, timing strip, work order, customer order form, timing strip, printing and cleaning report, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 994)
    - 135.0191A, Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 995)
    - 135.0191A-135.0194A, Printing and negative cleaning report, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 996)
    - 135.0192, Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 997)
    - 135.0193A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 998)
    - 135.0193A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 999)
    - 135.0194A, Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 1000)
    - 135.0195A, Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 1001)
    - 135.0195A-135.0198A Printing and negative cleaning report, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 1002)
    - 135.0196A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 1003)
    - 135.0197A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 1004)
    - 135.0198A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 1005)
    - 135.0199A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 1006)
    - 135.0199A-135.0202A printing and negative cleaning report, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 1007)
    - 135.0200A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 1008)
    - 135.0201A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 1009)
    - 135.0202A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 1010)
    - 135.0203A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 1011)
    - 135.0203A-135.0206A printing and negative cleaning report, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 1012)
    - 135.0204A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 1013)
    - 135.0205A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 1014)
    - 135.0206A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 1015)
    - 135.0209A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 1016)
    - 135.0209A-135.0214A printing and negative cleaning report, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 1017)
    - 135.0210A Edge bumber note, undated (Box 23, Folder 1018)
    - 135.0211A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 1019)
    - 135.0212A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 1020)
    - 135.0213A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 1021)
    - 135.0214A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 1022)
    - 135.0215A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 1023)
    - 135.0215A-135.0220A printing and negative cleaning report, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 1024)
    - 135.0216A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 1025)
    - 135.0217A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 1026)
    - 135.0218A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 1027)
    - 135.0219A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 1028)
    - 135.0220A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 1029)
    - 135.0240A Timer's listing, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 1030)
    - 135.0242A Timer's Listing, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 1031)
    - 135.0423A-135.0244A timer's listing, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 1032)
  - Subseries C: Production materials
    - Auditor's report, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 1033)
    - Biographical information, Frank Moore and Jim Self, undated (Box 23, Folder 1034)
    - Budgets, 1985-1987 (Box 23, Folder 1035)
    - Camera Reports, ca. 1987 (Box 23, Folder 1036)
    - Camera shot list and filming notes, undated (Box 23, Folder 1037)
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 23, Folder 1038)
    - Currency exchange, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 1039)
    - Dialogue scripts, undated (Box 25, Folder 1040)
    - DuArt film laboratories, 1985-1987 (Box 25, Folder 1041)
    - Fabric, undated (Box 25, Folder 1042)
    - Film and Video Arts, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 1043)
    - Grant applications, miscellaneous and partial., 1986 (Box 25, Folder 1044)
    - Insurance, undated (Box 25, Folder 1045)
    - Lighting, undated (Box 25, Folder 1046)
    - Mother's Sound Stages, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 1047)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 1048)
    - New York State Council on the Arts, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 1049)
    - Notes and miscellaneous papers, undated (Box 25, Folder 1050)
    - Payroll, undated (Box 25, Folder 1051)
    - phone lists, undated (Box 25, Folder 1052)
    - Photographs, taken during production, undated (Box 26, Folder data_value_missing_5c2c36bab5d9cf636fd0237a70f6655a)
    - Primary Performance Group general lEdger, account lists, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 1053)
    - Principal Credits, undated (Box 25, Folder 1054)
    - Production Budget worksheet, undated (Box 25, Folder 1055)
    - Production/rehearsal schedules, undated (Box 25, Folder 1056)
    - Provost Displays, undated (Box 25, Folder 1057)
    - PS 1 proposal, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 1058)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 25, Folder 1059)
    - Receipts, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 1060)
    - Rental notes, undated (Box 25, Folder 1061)
    - Scene breakdown, undated (Box 25, Folder 1062)
    - Sketches, undated (Box 25, Folder 1063)
    - Storyboard, complete, undated (Box 25, Folder 1064)
    - Storyboard fragments and copies, undated (Box 25, Folder 1065)
    - Summary of The Miller's Wife, undated (Box 25, Folder 1066)
    - Tax exemption paperwork, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 1067)
    - Time Chart, undated (Box 25, Folder 1068)
    - Titles, drawn by Frank Moore, undated (Box 25, Folder 1069)
    - WNET/Media Alliance. On-Line program application, undated (Box 25, Folder 1070)
  - Subseries D: Promotional Materials
    - Photographic stills, undated (Box 26, Folder data_value_missing_0b0cf2912f83332e68fc4ba1d488fb2c)
    - Postcard invitations, undated (Box 25, Folder 1071)
  - Subseries E: Artifacts
    - broken glass, undated (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_468a96dc70fba15c0d2198bbbdcd3d19)
  - Subseries F: Video Recordings - Access Copies
    - The Millers Wife - Work Sample (Master), [1987]; ID: 135.0292 (Box Shared Fales 150, Dvd 135.0292)
      TRT: 00:04:30
      Original Format: 3/4" Umatic
      Source ID: 135.0256
    - The Miller's Wife - Work Sample, [1987]; ID: 135.0280 (Box Shared Fales 131, Cd 135.0280)
      Source ID: 135.0257
    - The Miller's Wife - Scratchtrack Master, [1987]; ID: 135.0290 (Box Shared Fales 150, Dvd 135.0290)
      TRT: 00:25:00
      Source ID: 135.0173
    - The Miller's Wife (w/ Scratchtrack), [1987]; ID: 135.0281 (Box Shared Fales 131, Cd 135.0281)
      Source ID: 135.0170
    - The Miller's Wife - Master of Roughcut, Silent, [1987]; ID: 135.0289 (Box Shared Fales 150, Dvd 135.0289)
      Source ID: 135.0172
    - The Miller's Wife - Silent Workprint, [1987]; ID: 135.0286 (Box Shared Fales 150, Dvd 135.0286)
      TRT: Approx.00:30:00
      Source ID: 135.0169
    - The Miller's Wife - (Work in Progress) from 16mm Print, [1987]; ID: 135.0291 (Box Shared Fales 150, Dvd 135.0291)
      Original Format: Umatic
      Source ID: 135.0255
  - Subseries G: Film - Access Copies
    Films have not been preserved and are not available for research.
- Series VII: Additional Moving Image and Sound Recordings
  Series VII contains media materials unrelated to either Beehive or The Miller's Wife. Subseries A contains the media materials themselves and subseries B contains production information.
  - Subseries A: Video and Sound Recordings - Access Copies
    - The Boogieman/ Aquaman-- Studies for a Work in Progress, Moore/ Self, undated; ID: 135.0282 (Box Shared Fales 150, Dvd 135.0282)
      TRT: 00:05:00
      Source ID: 135.0265
    - Crankhouse, DTW, 6/1/1988-- Frank Moore/ Jim Self, ID: 135.0283 (Box Shared Fales 150, Dvd 135.0283)
      TRT: 00:57:00
      Source ID: 135.0262
    - Ruban Rouge, undated; ID: 135.0284 (Box Shared Fales 150, Dvd 135.0284)
      TRT: 00:01:40
      Source ID: 135.0267
    - A Tribute to Frank Moore, a Film by Rebecca Moore and Denise Zmekhol, Undated; ID: 135.0293 (Box Shared Fales 150, Dvd 135.0293, Dvd 135.0294)
      TRT: 00:12:00
      Also available on Blu-Ray Disc - ID: 135.0294
  - Subseries B: Video and Sound Recordings and Motion Picture Film - Originals
    Subseries B contains all original material. Researcher access is limited to Subseries A. Please see Fales Archivist.
    - Frank Moore / Jim Self - "Crankhouse" [2 versions]; approx. 00:53:00 min.; appears to be 2 versions of "Crankhouse", (1)-30 minutes (2)-23 minutes. Both taped at Dance Theater Workshop, June 1, 1988. (Box 25A, Folder ID: 135.0261)
      Videorecording, 3/4" Umatic, Fuji 60-min. videocassette
    - Frank Moore / Jim Self - "Crankhouse" Dance Theater Workshop (DTW) June 1, 1988. (Box 25A, Folder ID: 135.0262)
      Videorecording, VHS, Kodak T-120 videocassette.
    - Jim Self / Frank Moore - Primary Performance Group, Three Excerpts: (1) Tuscaloosa, (2) Camellia, (3) Beehive [Master tape]., undated (Box 25A, Folder ID: 135.0263)
      Videorecording, 3/4" Umatic, Kodak KCS 20-EB 930 videocassette.
    - Jim Self and Dancers, "Excerpts 1981". (Box 25A, Folder ID: 135.0264)
      Videorecording, 3/4" Umatic, Scotch videocassette.
    - Frank Moore / Jim Self - The Boogieman, Aquaman: Studies for a work in progress, 6 minutes, silent., undated (Box 25A, Folder ID: 135.0265)
      Videorecording, VHS, EK T-30 videocassette.
    - PG Interview, 21 August 1985. (Box 25A, Folder ID: 135.0266)
      Videorecording, 3/4" Umatic, UCA 20s videocassette.
    - Ruban Rouge., undated (Box 25A, Folder ID: 135.0267)
      Videorecording, VHS Maxell T-120 P/I Plus videocassette.
    - Shaman-Mattox July, 1984. Side A: (1) Charlie, (2) Shaman-I (early version, Bob Weir- Shamanic voices, George Marsh- congas, cymbals), (3) Shaman-II synthesis only. Side B: (1) Shaman-III (Mel Graves-Bass), (2) Shaman-IV (excerpt from opening- Bob Ernst- voice of death.) (Box 25A, Folder ID: 135.0268)
      Audiorecording, Pacific Stereo 90-minute audiocassette.
    - Undeveloped motion picture film, 1987; 7 media elements Seven rolls of 16mm film, undeveloped.
    - Beehive, digital audio tape (Box Shared Fales PM 38, Case 135.0276)
    - Whitney Biennial, undated (Box 70, Vhs 135.0261)
    - Self/Moore (Video: Christine Tyrnell), 1988-07-22 (Box 70, Vhs 135.0262)
    - Robert Neal Fulps In Memorium, April 1991 (Box 70, Vhs 135.0266)
    - Frank Moore Memorial Audiocassette, 2002 (Box 70, Audiocassette 135.0267)
  - Subseries C: Production Information
    - Blue Grotto, undated (Box 25, Folder 1072)
    - Camellia. Notes regarding the rights and reproduction of the piece as well as a draft of the agreement with Dick Connette, undated (Box 25, Folder 1073)
- Series VIII: Artifacts and Objects
  This series contains artifacts and objects relating to Frank Moore's life and artwork. The series is divided into three subseries. Subseries A: Personal artifacts includes objects such as x-rays. Subseries B: Art Implements and Artifacts includes materials such as paint brushes. Subseries C: Miscellaneous includes objects such as the original AIDS ribbons. This series is organized alphabetically.
  - Subseries A: Personal Items
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 25, Folder 1074)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 25, Folder 1075)
    - X-Rays and report. Chest and lungs. American Hospital of Paris. November-December 1977 and January 1978 [additional materials in oversize box], 1977-1978 (Box 25, Folder 1076)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 25, Folder 1077)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 25, Folder 1078)
    - X-rays and report. Chest. Mt. Sinai Hospital [additional materials in oversize box] March 1979 (Box 25, Folder 1079)
    - X-rays. Nasal bones, New York, May 13, 1980 [additional materials in oversize box] (Box 25, Folder 1080)
    - Wallet including driver's license, membership cards and metrocard, undated (Box 28, Folder data_value_missing_8c7e740beded1d0da5508942b686440d)
  - Subseries B: Art Implements and Artifacts
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 25, Folder 1081)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 25, Folder 1082)
    - Item removed to oversize, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 1083)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 25, Folder 1084)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 25, Folder 1085)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 25, Folder 1087)
    - Brushes, trowel style painting knife, burnisher made of wood and agate., undated (Box 28, Folder data_value_missing_e27f215bbc9adaec19a30756947e6137)
    - Diamond shapes, cut out of envelopes, undated (Box 25, Folder 1088)
    - DNA transparency, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 1089)
    - Dress sketches. Found in A History of Costume, undated (Box 25, Folder 1090)
    - Enlargement of torture graphic, undated (Box 25, Folder 1091)
    - HIV illustrations, ink-jet prints and acetates, undated (Box 25, Folder 1092)
    - Lettering examples, undated (Box 25, Folder 1093)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 25, Folder 1094)
    - Molds. [perhaps of feathers], undated (Box 29, Folder data_value_missing_339f2f8de1b7cbb56ac1477b2cfd3e35)
    - Photo mat, undated (Box 25, Folder 1095)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 25, Folder 1096)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 25, Folder 1097)
    - Sketch board, undated (Box 25, Folder 1098)
    - small organisms. green ink on beige paper, undated (Box 25, Folder 1099)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 25, Folder 1100)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 25, Folder 1101)
    - Stencils, pills, undated (Box 25, Folder 1102)
  - Subseries C: Miscellaneous
    - Bee on a string, undated (Box 28, Folder data_value_missing_edcf04c736ac377b8ff5ccf01652d4eb)
    - Beanie, purple, pink and white, undated (Box 28, Folder data_value_missing_52c73a2102a852ce66de1422c1e8ac59)
    - Confederate States of America fifty dollar bill, 1864 (Box 25, Folder 1103)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 25, Folder 1104)
    - Mask, foam., undated (Box 28, Folder data_value_missing_a723f6084563aae4b9ba8e578cfb6312)
    - Name tag from Academy Award in Art function., undated (Box 28, Folder data_value_missing_d6ee725819e1887797a1ac84a4453a21)
    - Pins [possibly hat pins], undated (Box 28, Folder data_value_missing_be81cede6bced6e808d277c5ae6cd5fc)
    - Pin. "Queer eyes, Queer-ize", undated (Box 28, Folder data_value_missing_c2f32e0f9861af85f30f0c048cf7a898)
    - Pouch. Plastic, zebra striped, pink lettering "Savage", undated (Box 28, Folder data_value_missing_34e8f35a71aca5eb0fac92d24d01a6bb)
    - Red ribbons. Used at "A Day Without Art" Original AIDS Ribbons, 1991 (Box 28, Folder data_value_missing_abd21ae3bd5be2d2d4b31c4342b93621)
    - Red Ribbon. Two large ribbons. "A Day Without AIDS" and "Work for a Cure", undated (Box 28, Folder data_value_missing_769d24d20720aa579b4dd7e132fe3aa1)
    - T-shirt, design by Kenny Scharf. Drawing of Betty from the Flintstones., undated (Box 28, Folder data_value_missing_d43f240296e5bb04ba8088ecd769e776)
- Series IX: Juvenalia and Family Memorabilia
  Series nine contains two subseries. Subseries A:Juvenalia, items relating to Frank Moore's life before his art career such as a year book and diploma. Subseries B: Family Memorabilia holds personal, family related information such as birth and death announcements.
  - Subseries A: Juvenalia
    - Broadside critiquing physical education program at Roslyn High School. Written by Richie Ruchman. Illustrated by Frank Moore., undated (Box 25, Folder 1105)
    - Roslyn High School Yearbook, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 1106)
    - School correspondence regarding Frank Moore, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 1107)
    - Selective Service classification, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 1108)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 25, Folder 1109)
  - Subseries B: Family Memorabilia
    - Birth Announcement, Violet Moore Schneider, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 1110)
    - Burt, Arthur Hartwell. Frank Moore's maternal grandfather. Photograph of Arthur Burt, vice president of Sherwin-Williams paints in Cleveland, Ohio., undated (Box 25, Folder 1111)
    - Dickinson, Blair. Memorial service program, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 1112)
    - Harris, John Rockwell. Materials regarding his memorial service. Harris was Frank Moore's stepbrother., 1990 (Box 25, Folder 1113)
    - Harris, Sarah Burt. Materials regarding her memorial service, she was Frank Moore's mother., 1997 (Box 25, Folder 1114)
    - Hodermarsky, Daniel. Memorial announcement. Hodermarsky was Frank Moore's uncle., 1999 (Box 25, Folder 1115)
    - Moore, Frank Charles. Frank Moore's paternal grandfather. Biography, Izaak Walton League address and Wherret Lecture publication. Frank C. Moore was Lieutenant Governor of New York., ca. 1951 (Box 25, Folder 1116)
    - Photographs, miscellaneous, undated (Box 25, Folder 1117)
- Series X: Printed Materials
  This series contains printed materials from Frank Moore's library including books, newspapers, magazines and art catalogues. Materials are organized alphabetically by author last name where available or alphabetically by title.
  - Subseries A: Brochures, Merchandise Catalogues, and Owner's Manuals
    - Appliance Owner's Manuals, undated (Box 25, Folder 1118)
    - Brushes for the Arts and Trades. General Catalogue. April 1956. (Box 25, Folder 1119)
    - Carroll Gardens Incorporated Plant Catalogue, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 1120)
    - French travel brochures, undated (Box 25, Folder 1121)
    - Home Depot Professional Equipment and Supply Catalogue, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 1122)
    - Libidinous Modernity. Babes and Horny catalogue, undateed (Box 25, Folder 1123)
    - Oil Colors, ca. 1998 (Box 25, Folder 1124)
    - Talas catalogue. Preservation, conservation and restoration supplies., undated (Box 25, Folder 1125)
    - Tourist information: Italy, undated (Box 25, Folder 1126)
    - Venini lighting, undated (Box 25, Folder 1127)
  - Subseries B: Artist Catalogues
    - Abstract Painting: 1960-1969 at PS 1, ca. 1982 (Box 25, Folder 1128)
    - L'Art de la Poterie en France de Rodin a Dufy. Exhibit of the national ceramics museum. June-October 1971. (Box 25, Folder 1129)
    - The art of the Real USA 1948-1968. Museum of Modern Art, New York, undated (Box 25, Folder 1130)
    - Art Treasures from the Vienna Collections 1949-1950 (Box 30, Folder 1131)
    - Francis Bacon at the Museo d'Arte Moderna., 1993 (Box 30, Folder 1132)
    - Bakker, Gabrielle at Mincher/Wilcox Gallery, San Francisco, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 1133)
    - Balthus: paintings and Drawings 1934-1977 at Pierre Matisse Gallery. (Box 30, Folder 1134)
    - Vanessa Bell 1879-1961 at Davis and Long COmpany, New York, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 1135)
    - Beyond Loss: Art in the Era of AIDS., 1993 (Box 30, Folder 1136)
    - James Bishop. Galerie nationale du Jeu de Paume., 1993 (Box 30, Folder 1137)
    - Probert Blanchon at the Lost Angeles Center for Photographic Studies., 1996-1997 (Box 30, Folder 1138)
    - Nancy Bowen and Nancy Davidson.Figuring the BOdy. at the Ezra and Cecile Zilkha Gallery., 1998 (Box 30, Folder 1139)
    - Gianni Burattoni, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 1140)
    - Giorgio de Chirico. Museum of Modern art. exhibit program cover., 1982 (Box 30, Folder 1141)
    - Christo and Jeanne-Claude: Early Works. Martin Gropius Bau, Berlin, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 1142)
    - Edgar Degas 1834-1917 at Wildenstein, NEw York, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 1143)
    - Charles Demuth Poster Portraits 1923-1929 at Yale University Art Gallery, New Haven., 1995 (Box 30, Folder 1144)
    - Derain. "Hommage a Derain" at La Galerie Paul Vallotton S.A., 1975 (Box 30, Folder 1145A)
    - A. Derain 1880-1954 at Galerie Schmit. May 12-June 20, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 1145B)
    - Andre Derain, 1880-1954. Paintings and Drawings at Theo Waddington and Co. Inc., New York., 1981 (Box 30, Folder 1146)
    - Andre Derain, 1880-1954. Watercolours, gouaches, mixed media from the period 1930-1953 at Victor Waddington, London., 1977 (Box 30, Folder 1147)
    - Raoul Dufy, ceramiques at Galerie LANDROT, Paris., 1990 (Box 30, Folder 1148)
    - Estrujenbank. March-April 1990. (Box 30, Folder 1149)
    - Expressive Heads at Jason McCoy Inc. New York May 6-June 12, 1993. (Box 30, Folder 1150)
    - Fantin-Latour: Flowers, Fruits, Figures at Scott and Fowles, New York. March 26-April 14, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 1151)
    - Futuruismo and Futurismi: oggetti futuristi [Futurist objects], 1986 (Box 30, Folder 1152)
    - Joy Garnett: Rocket Science at Debs and Co. New York., 2001 (Box 30, Folder 1153)
    - Alan Glass: 1971-1991 at Claude Bernard Gallery, New York. (Box 30, Folder 1154)
    - Gnoli, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 1155)
    - Stephen Hannock at James Graham and Sons, New York., 1996 (Box 30, Folder 1156)
    - Stephen Hannock: Space and Time at Charles P. Russell Gallery, Deerfield MA and Dayton Art Institute, Dayton Ohio., 1998-1999 (Box 30, Folder 1157)
    - Geoffrey Hendricks: Day into Night, 1993-1994 (Box 30, Folder 1158)
    - Florence Henri, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 1159)
    - Elana Herzog: The Carpet Prardigm at Ezra and Cecile Zilkha Gallery, Wesleyan University., 1998 (Box 30, Folder 1160A)
    - David Hockney: New Paintings, Drawings and Graphics at Andre Emmerich Gallery, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 1160B)
    - James Hyde at John Good Gallery, New York., 1989 (Box 30, Folder 1161)
    - Win Knowlton at The Museum of Modern Art., 1986 (Box 30, Folder 1162)
    - Leo Lionni: il tavolo nero at Galleria Giulia, Rome and Galleria Eva Menzio, Torino. inscribed., 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 1163)
    - Leo Lionni: dipanit, sculture, disegni. at Galleria del Milione., 1972 (Box 30, Folder 1164)
    - Lazar el Lissitzky. Architectural Models: Lenin Tribune 1920/1924., 1984 (Box 30, Folder 1165)
    - Man Ray: Sotheby's auction catalog., 1995 (Box 30, Folder 1166)
    - John Marin Etchings 1905-1951 at Marlborough Fine Art, New York., 1971 (Box 30, Folder 1167)